https://www.dwscientific.com/privacy-policy

Contact Us sales@dwscientific.co.uk +44 (0)1274 595728 en
Search Login
ProductsBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationProductsAnaerobic Workstations Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationAnaerobic WorkstationsView AllA20A25A35A45A55A85A95A135 HEPAA135 GMPA155 HEPADG250Jar Gassing SystemHypoxic Workstations Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationHypoxic WorkstationsView AllH25H35H45H85H95H135 HEPAH135 GMPH155 HEPAi2Microaerobic Workstations Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationMicroaerobic WorkstationsView AllM35M45M85M95M135 HEPAM155 HEPAGMP Compliant Workstations Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationGMP Compliant WorkstationsView AllA135 GMP Anaerobic WorkstationH135 GMP HypoxystationJars and Gassing Systems Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationJars and Gassing SystemsView AllWhitley Jar Gassing SystemAnaerobic JarsBacterial Enumeration Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationBacterial EnumerationView AllWhitley WASP TouchVacuum Source 602Whitley Automated Spiral PlaterLab Automation Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationLab AutomationView AllWalk Away Specimen ProcessorCYCLONE™PhenoMATRIX™ Software SuiteMALDI-TraceRadian™Sample Preparation Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationSample PreparationView AllDILUWELMIXWELDOSYWELMedia Preparation Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationMedia PreparationView AllMEDIAWEL 10MEDIAWEL 30DISTRIWEL440Nanodac Chart RecorderRefurbished Media Preparators From £8,000Liquid Handling Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationLiquid HandlingView AllWhitley AsPROvacPOLYWEL 3DDOSYWELColony Counting/Zone Reading Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationColony Counting/Zone ReadingView AllaCOLyte 3ProtoCOL3 PlusChromaZonaProtos 3AutoCOLTissue Engineering Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationTissue EngineeringView AllTEB1000 BioreactorTEB500 BioreactorTC-3 BioreactorTC-3F BioreactorAutoclaving Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationAutoclavingView AllTuttnauer 2840EL AutoclaveTuttnauer 3850EL AutoclaveTuttnauer 5050EL AutoclaveTuttnauer 5075EL AutoclaveTuttnauer 2840EL AutoclaveTuttnauer 3850EL AutoclaveTuttnauer 3870ELV AutoclaveTuttnauer 5075ELV AutoclaveNanodac Chart RecorderImaging Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationImagingView AllWhitley PetrifotoCytoSMART™ Lux2CytoSMART™ Lux3 FLRapid Methods Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationRapid MethodsView AllRABITGeneral Laboratory Products Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationGeneral Laboratory ProductsView AllMini IncubatorAutomatic Gas Changeover UnitIntroduction to Clinical Anaerobic BacteriologySecond Hand Equipment Back from sub navigationClose sub navigationSecond Hand EquipmentView AllDG250 Anaerobic WorkstationS8000 Media Preparator (metal cover)S8000 Media Preparator (plastic cover)Whitley Automated Spiral PlaterWASP Touch (ex demo)ConsumablesBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationConsumablesWhitley WorkstationsBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationWhitley WorkstationsHEPA FilterRacks & TagsCatalyst & AnotoxAirlock TraysSleeves, Cuffs, GauntletsMiscellaneousSpiral PlatingBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationSpiral PlatingDisposable BeakersBottles & CapsPowdered InkCounting TablesWater PotsLab AutomationBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationLab AutomationPrinter SuppliesDrip TraysCleansing SolutionsDocking StationMedia/Sample PreparationBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationMedia/Sample PreparationPre-cut TubingTubing SetsFiltersPrinter LabelsMiscellaneousTissue EngineeringBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationTissue EngineeringP3D ChambersGripsRABITBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationRABITImpedance CellsIndirect Method TubesRubber BungsAutoclavesBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationAutoclavesAutoclave Printer PaperDeodorising and CleaningMicrofluidic ModellingBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationMicrofluidic ModellingBe-Flow2D3Be-Flow ChipBe-TransFlow ChipBe-Gradient ChipLiquid HandlingBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationLiquid HandlingTubingMiscellaneousGeneral Laboratory ProductsBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationGeneral Laboratory ProductsAnaerobic JarsBatteriesFoam CleanserLabdet100Service & AccreditationBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationService & AccreditationService & AccreditationUKAS Calibration / ValidationService Video UploadService Support FormContract LaboratoryAboutBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationAboutCorporateBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationCorporateAbout UsHistoryProducts & ServicesTestimonialsCNC MachiningEnvironmental PolicyCustomer ResourcesBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationCustomer ResourcesPublished PapersCorporate Information/LiteratureCertificatesWorkstation Poster GrantVirtual Meeting AwardAnaerobic Sample TransportData Download Software RegistrationExportBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationExportExport SalesOverseas DistributorsEventsBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationEventsExhibitions2nd Whitley Hypoxia SymposiumP&CMAN CourseWorking for DWSBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationWorking for DWSDWS Apprenticeship SchemeJoin the TeamBlogContact UsBack from sub navigationClose sub navigationContact UsContact UK, DE, AU or USSign up for News Bulletin
Request a Callback
HomePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Got a Question?
Request a Callback
The privacy policy outlined below can be found on the Don Whitley Scientific website and is accessible to everyone who visits the website. There are also several instances when a data subject may be directed to read the Privacy Policy to ensure they are aware of our processing procedures and reasons for collecting their data.
This document is approved by the directors prior to publication on any DWS external website.
This privacy policy sets out how Don Whitley Scientific Limited (DWS) uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.
Data from the website is collected by our Data Processor, Rejuvenate Productions, the company that hosts the Don Whitley Scientific website. Don Whitley Scientific is the Data Controller and is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected in line with the Data Protection Act 1998. If we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Don Whitley Scientific may make changes to this policy as it is reviewed once a year during a data protection compliance audit to make sure it still accurately covers what data we collect, what we do with the data and our policy for protecting personal data.
What personal information we may collect
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
What we do with the information we gather
We may collect this information to allow us to contact you to deal with your request or enquiry; to understand your needs and to provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
If you have registered for our news bulletins we will periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting, using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone or mail.
We may also collect information that monitors activity whilst you use this website or if you share any of its content by clicking the social media buttons. This information is purely analytical data and no personal details are stored against this information.
Your personal data will never be shared with any third party organisations other than where we have a legal duty to do so.
Legal basis for processing your data
Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it.
We will normally collect personal information from you only (i) where we have your consent to do so, (ii) where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you, or (iii) where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your rights. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Data retention
We retain personal information we collect from you where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, to provide you with a service you have requested).
When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we delete your data from our system, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.
What are cookies?
Cookies are small text files containing pieces of information that websites can store on your computer's hard disk. Cookies enable users to navigate around the website and (where appropriate) allow us to continually improve the website and make it more efficient to use on future visits.
We use two types of cookies on this website:
Session cookies are temporary cookies that remain on your machine only for as long as you are on the website and are deleted after each visit.
Persistent cookies which remain on your machine until expiry or deletion (many of these have automatic deletion dates). Persistent cookies may store your personal preferences, for example your language preferences on multi-lingual sites. They may also be used to record activity you may have previously completed, such as completing an online survey, so that you are not asked to complete the survey every time you use the site.
How we use cookies on our website
We use some 'strictly necessary' cookies within our online services. These are limited to those deemed essential to provide you with the services you have requested therefore must be allowed to continue with that service.
In addition, we use cookies to:
Collect anonymous information that will help us understand visitor browsing habits on our website; compile statistical reports on website activity, e.g. number of visitors and the pages they visit; in some cases, remember information about you when you visit our site. We may need to do this to provide some of our services.
We sometimes use third parties to assist us in the analysis of visits to and performance of our website, but no personal information is collected and no personal information is sent to the third parties for this purpose.
We do not use cookies to track your use of the internet after you leave our site, nor do we use them to store any personal information in them that others could read and understand.
Changing your cookie settings
You can block any cookies from any website through your browser settings. For more specific information about how to do this and how to manage cookies to suit your preferences, including deleting those that have already been added to your computer, please visit www.aboutcookies.org.
If you share the use of a computer, accepting or rejecting the use of cookies will affect all users of that computer.
Consent to cookies
If you continue to use this site without disabling cookies we will take that as your consent for us to place cookies on your computer. Please remember if you do disable cookies then some parts of our website may not work properly and you will not be able to use some of our services.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest or social media platforms. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over other websites. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and they are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that requests you to tick to confirm your consent to receiving a limited amount of direct marketing.
If you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by completing the ‘Contact Us’ form, or by clicking ‘Unsubscribe’ at the bottom of any e-bulletin sent via Mailchimp.
If you have any privacy-related questions or unresolved problems, you may contact us by completing the ‘Contact Us’ form.
You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority. (Contact details for data protection authorities in the European Economic Area, Switzerland and certain non-European countries (including the US and Canada) are available here.)
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998 and the General Data Protection Regulations 2016 (GDPR). No administration fee will be charged for considering and/or complying with such a request unless the request is deemed to be unnecessary or excessive in nature.
We maintain a procedure in order to help you confirm that your personal information remains correct and up-to-date or choose whether or not you wish to receive material from us or some of our partners. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, or if you would like a copy of the information held on you please complete the ‘Contact Us’ form on our website as stated above and we will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Terms and Conditions
Cookie Policy
Privacy Policy
Sitemap
sales@dwscientific.co.uk
+44 (0)1274 595728
Facebook iconLinkedIn iconTwitter iconYouTube icon
Don Whitley Scientific Limited. Registered in England no. 1342672. Registered Office: Victoria Works, Victoria Street, Bingley, West Yorkshire, BD16 2NH, UK
© 2020 Don Whitley Scientific Limited Copyright: All rights reserved - No content can be reproduced without our prior written consent.
Web Design - Rejuvenate Digital
Login
en
Search
Contact Us
sales@dwscientific.co.uk
+44 (0)1274 595728
Choose a Country
If you are based in Germany or Australia, please select the website of our subsidiary company there. A different selection of products is available in these countries. Otherwise, please select ‘English’ and you will be able to find your local distributor in the ‘Overseas Distributors’ section.
English
Australian
Deutsch
Contact UsWe are here to help
Product Search
Search
Share this
Please select your preferred language from the list below
Facebook Twitter Pinterest WhatsApp Email*:
Login
Sign in
Forgot your password? Click Here
